<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ernesto Mendoza</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ernesto Mendoza</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>R and Python</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/06/r-and-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/06/r-and-python/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! This website is a compilation of my resume and projects that I completed while taking Computational Biology at UT. The projects were done using both R and Python, I hope everyone likes them!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA Draft-2018-2019_Project1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: My dataset is Water-column environmental variables and accompanying discrete CTD measurements collected offshore the U.S. Mid- and South Atlantic. There are many variables but to name a few, there is SHIP, the name of the boat in which the samples were taken, the SITE, the location of the samples taken, the Depth(m), Temperature(C), Conductivity(mS/cm), Turbidity, Conventional Radiocarbon Age, Salinity, and the dissolved Inorganic concentrations of Phoshpate/Silicate/Nitrate/Nitrite/Ammonia. There were thousands of observations in the original dataset but after manipulating the data, I uploaded 45 observations for each variable into R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
